On a basic, basic, very, very, very basic level,
trans people are the physical embodiment
of the shift that has to be made
out of the binary that has us trapped.
Their existence is revolutionary.
Even when they're completely terrible,
like Caitlyn Jenner,
who just found out that they can't travel
because of new rules,
that Trump has put in place.
Even in her ridiculousness,
her existence is revolutionary.
So when you protect trans rights,
you're literally being revolutionary
for many, many reasons.
One of them, because you're disrupting the system
that's kept you in a chokehold of either or,
knowing full well there are many more options,
particularly more options than
this that we're in
or this that they offer us.
We can make up our own shit.
Get it?
Shout out to the trans folks
for teaching us how it's done.
It's gotta be a better way.